surfagain.com 2014-05-25

# Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used on all [Third Rail Holdings web sites](http://www.thirdrailholdings.com/electrifying_media_web_sites.php). To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on Third Rail Holdings websites. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, utilize information services, store electronic data such as photos, videos and music, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages may vary and may include: 

Name   
Address   
Age   
Gender   
Personal Preferences   
Email address   
Phone number   
Credit/Debit Card Information 

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you will need to submit the recipient's address. In this circumstance, the types of personal information collected are: 

Name   
Address   
Age   
Gender   
Personal Preferences   
Email address   
Phone number 

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order or request for services to complete that order. We my share this information with outside parties to such extent they can provide you with additional products, services and information which may be of interest to you. 

We use the information you provide about someone else when placing an order or request for services to complete that order. We my share this information with outside parties to such extent they can provide them with additional products, services and information which may be of interest to them. 

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses may be used by third parties to present offers which may be of interest to you. 

You can register with any Third Rail Holdings website if you would like to receive our catalog as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. 

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design the Third Rail Holdings websites and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at any Third Rail Holdings website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of any Third Rail Holdings website is structured to attract anyone under 13. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging in to the Third Rail Holdings website you registered with initially. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. 

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please [contact us](http://www.thirdrailholdings.com/contact_us.php) via our [on-line form](http://www.thirdrailholdings.com/contact_us.php) or via our postal mailing Address: _PMB 08346, Morgantown W.Va. 26507-0877_.
